alright guys welcome back to the last tutorial in this little mini series and
正常的家伙 欢迎回来 到最后 这个小迷你 系列的教程和
of course right now what we did is we went to a web page we got all the words
当然，我们现在所做的 就是我们 去了一个网页， 我们得到了所有的话
we have them in the list of nice clean words without any stupid symbols so now
我们将它们放在干净清单中 现在没有任何愚蠢符号的单词
we just need to create a dictionary a dictionary of course consisting of each
我们只需要创建 一个字典a 当然字典由每个组成
word and how many times appeared in the webpage very simple stuff so I'm going
这个词和多少次出现在 网页很简单， 所以我要去
to make a function called great dictionary and of course we need to pass
制作一个名为 great 的函数 字典，当然我们需要通过
it in our nice clean word list right there and now since we're actually
它在我们干净的单词列表中 从那以后我们就在 那里
saying that we're going to create a function let's go ahead and create the
说我们要创造 一个 功能，让我们继续前进， 创造
function so that's our function name Pesta than that looking good so the
函数， 这是我们的函数名称 佩斯比那看起来好看所以
first thing we need is to create a blank dictionary that's going to store all of
我们需要的第一件事是 创建 一个空白 将存储所有 的 字典
the words so I'm just going to name it word count and of course the create
这些话我就这么说了 字数，当然还有创造
blank dictionary just set equal to two little curly braces right there so now
空白字典只设置 为 两个 现在，那里有小花括号
what we want to do is we're essentially just going to loop through our list of
我们想要做的是我们本质 只是循环遍历我们的列表
words so I'll just put on I'll just name it forward in clean word list and not
单词所以我只是穿上我只会 命名 它在干净的单词列表中前进而不是
work or war or reset now for each word it's actually going to be really easy
现在为每个单词工作或战争 或 重置 它实际上 很容易
what we want to do is we want to say okay if that word is already in the
我们想做的 是我们想说的 好吧，如果那个词已经在
dictionary then just add one to whatever the current count is if it's not in
字典然后只需添加 一个 当前计数是否不在
there yet then create an entry for it and set it equal to one since it's the
然后为它创建一个条目 并设置它 等于一，因为 它是
first time coming across that word so we'll say if word in word count then
第一次 跨越这个 词 来 所以我们会说，如果单词计数那么
this means that it already came across that word before it's already in your
这意味着它已经遇到过 在它之前已经存在的那个词
dictionary so all we need to do is take the word count
字典所以我们需要 做的就是采取 字数
so in this dictionary whatever that word is add 1 to the value of it so if it
所以在这本词典中 无论那个词 是它的值加1， 如果它
came across it nine times before it would add one to it of course I know
在它之前遇到过它九次 当然我知道会加 一个
it's self-explanatory so else this is going to occur if it's the first
这是不言自明的 如果它是第一个，这将会发生
time coming across the word so I can actually copy this and if it's your
时间 过 了这个词，所以我可以 实际上复制这个，如果它是你的
first time coming across the word then add that word to the dictionary and set
第 一次 遇到这个词 将该单词添加到 字典 并设置
the value equal to one or the counter equal to one whatever you want to call
的值等于 一个 或计数器 等于你要打电话的任何一个
it so now with this loop we created a dictionary that stores each word in that
现在，通过这个循环，我们创建了一个 存储每个单词的字典
webpage and it also stores the frequency or amount of times that that word
网页 ，它还存储频率 或该词的次数
occurred so that's all we have but right now our dictionary is just whatever
我们所拥有的一切都是正确的 现在我们的字典就是什么
order it was processed and and it's unsorted of course what we want to do is we want to sort our dictionary based on
订单它被处理了，它是 当然没有解决我们想要做的事情 我们希望我们的字典基础上进行排序
the frequency of the words that occurred so I don't want to go and scroll through
中 发生的词的频率 所以我不想去滚动浏览
everything and try to look for the highest one I want a program to do that so how do we sort a dictionary by the
并试着去寻找 最高的我想要一个 程序来做到这一点 那么我们如何按字典排序字典呢？
value well all we do is this for there's actually a bunch of different ways but
值以及所有我们要做的就是本作有 实际上是一堆不同的 方式但是
this is actually a really easy one so for key value because we're looping
这其实是一个非常简单的一个 ，这样 为了关键值，因为我们正在循环
through a dictionary and sorted now sorted basically takes the first
通过字典 并现在排序 排序基本上是第一个
parameter is saying what do you want to sort well we just want to sort this dictionary word count and we want to go
参数是说你想要什么 好吧，我们只想对此进行排序 字典字数，我们想去
through each items and this is pretty much saying arm I don't know it's just
通过每个项目，这很 漂亮 很多说 胳膊 我不知道它只是
saying you need to give it a bunch of items to sort now each dictionary item
说你需要给 它一堆 要对每个字典项进行排序的项目
is made up of a key and a value the key is the word like we learned and the
由一把钥匙和一把钥匙组成 就像我们学到的这个词一样
value is the frequency so it would be like - not 18 Bucky 4 so what we want to do is if we just
值是频率所以这 将是 喜欢- 不是18 Bucky 4 所以我们想做的就是我们
sort it by the key it's going to sort an alphabetic order if we sort it by the
按它要 排序 的 键 排序 字母顺序，如果我们按照它排序
value it's going to sort in numerical order so this is kind of confusing um a
价值它将按数字排序 这是一种令人困惑 的问题
parameter of sorted because it uses key what it's not talking about the
sort的参数因为它使用了key 它不是在谈论 什么
dictionary key whenever we pass it in the parameter and sorted function is
传递它时，字典键 参数 和排序函数是
saying the key is basically tell me what you want to sort by so we want to sort
说关键基​​本上是告诉我什么 你想排序，所以我们想排序
by operator item getter one so what's this mean well
由运营商 物品得到一个 所以这意味着什么
like I said what operator does is it's basically something that we import it
就像我说的操作员所做的那样 基本上我们导入它的东西
and they just allows you to work with the built-in data types in Python so it's not really important it's nothing
他们 只是让你 一起 工作 Python中的内置数据类型 它并不重要，没什么
that we have to memorize now what item getter is is it basically says okay I'm
我们现在必须记住什么项目 getter是它基本上说 好吗 我是
going to go to your dictionary and I'm going to get an item from your
要去你的字典，我 要从你的物品中获取物品
dictionary to survive now your dictionary each entry only has two
字典， 现在你的生存 字典每个条目 只有两个
specific items it's composed of a key and a value so if we wrote 0 it would sort by key we want to sort by the value
特定项目由一个密钥组成 和一个值，所以如果我们写0它会 按键排序我们希望 按 值 排序
so we're going to pass it in 1 simple enough so now all we have to do
所以我们将在 1中 传递它 现在 我们所要做的就是 这么简单
is now that we got a nice sorted dictionary we just need to print it out
现在我们 得到了一个很好的排序 字典，我们只需要打印 出来
so key and value and this is going to print out a nice hopefully sorted
左右键和价值，这是 怎么回事 打印出一个很好的希望排序
dictionary so check that out so actually you see how this is sorted
字典所以检查出来 所以实际上你看到它是如何排序的
by value now so the word a occurred 34 times the word I don't know about
现在按价值， 所以单词a出现了34 我不知道的那个词
occurred 6 I show you guys what I was talking about with this if we sort it by
发生了6 我 告诉 你们 我是谁 如果我们按照它来解决这个问题
the 0 with item in other words the key of course that's when it sorts by
0表示项目，换句话说是键 当然那就是它排序的时候
alphabetical order and we don't want that we want to sort by the value or the
字母顺序，我们不想要 我们想 按 值或者 排序
amount of times the word occurred so that's what we get so in this webpage
这个词发生的次数 这就是我们在这个 网页上得到的
the most frequently occurring word was a and if we scroll down all the unique
最常出现的一句话是 如果我们向下滚动所有唯一的
words or this feature through great Hungary clearly inch encourage all that
通过伟大的话语或 这个功能 匈牙利明显鼓励所有这一切
stuff so that ladies and gentlemen is how you make a word counter or a
东西让 女士们，先生们是 你怎么做一个单词计数器或一个
frequency counter and Python and again you can use this for a bunch of stuff
频率计数器和 Python，并 再次 你可以用它 来做一堆东西
search engines use this to find out what content is your website related to if
搜索引擎使用它来找出什么 内容 是您的网站 与if相关
you ever make an ad network then you would look at this it says and say okay so this website must be related
你永远做一个广告网络，那么 你 会看着它说，并说 好 所以这个网站必须是相关的
tutorials in bacon which pretty much that's all my web
几乎 是培根的教程 这就是我的网络
it is so it would put ads about tutorials and bacon on there and well if
它是如此广告 教程和培根在那里，如果
you ever were just interested in maybe your own blog saying okay what words do
你可能 只对它感兴趣 你自己的博客说好话用什么词
I use more than I should okay I should probably start stop typing
我使用的比我应该的多 好吧我应该开始停止输入
a every other sentence you know you can do something like that so hopefully it helped you out and also as always if you
每一个句子等，你知道 你 可以 做这样的事情，所以 希望它 帮助你，也像往常一样帮助你
want any of the source code from this tutorial then just go to my forum and
想 从 这个 任何 的源代码 教程然后 去我的论坛和
I'm going to be posting it all in the Python section right here so uh well
我将把它全部发布在 Python部分就在这里呃 好吧
that's it and also if you have any tips for improvements or if you want to offer
这就是它， 如果你有 任何提示 改进或如果你想 提供
any suggestions on how this can be better maybe taking out some common
关于这是怎么回事的任何建议 更好的可能是一些常见的
words then join the discussion we would love to have you but for now thank you
然后加入我们的讨论 喜欢拥有你，但现在谢谢你
guys for watching don't forget to subscribe I'll see you next time
观看的人不要忘了 订阅 我 下次 再见